my adolescence feels like it started
what my childhood ended in loss with the
ending of Christianity in my life when I
started to question the infallibility of
the Bible in the gospel and I couldn't
make logical sense of it and I wasn't
allowed to question it I had not been
allowed to question expecting to take it
on faith made me not be able to have
faith in it and so this deep important
part of me this truth I held very
strongly to fellow--a and that was huge
and I started to cling much more
strongly to logic and science and make
sure that I was never duped never found
out something I held so true would be
made false so I just never held anything
so true and if I did it was based on
logic and science and even then 99.9%
certain my adolescence was very
different than my childhood because
unlike my childhood where I went to
seven different elementary schools I
went to the same junior high school for
three years that then funneled into the
high school that all of those junior
high kids went to so I went effectively
I went to school with the same kids for
six years but my friendship group
changed every year and a half to two
years I can trace a lot of the
experiences I had the guys I dated and
the friends that I was friends with
people I ended up being best friends
with to this one event that I went like
on a Tuesday night we went to him
because it was cheap movie night and
afterwards this group of thirteen girls
that went to a movie we weren't all
friends we were kind of acquaintances
and it was a bunch of friends together
but having gone to McDonald's after if I
hadn't been there we wouldn't have met
these two groups of guys who became one
group became like the love of my life
and one of my best friends married one
of the guys and one of the other ones
had like a unrequited love thing with
the third one and then the other group
became what was a few guys that I dated
as well as my best friend who may be the
necklace and is no longer on the planet
and so it's weird to all the trace so
much of what happens to you back to that
event including I went on a German
exchange it's changed with a German
exchange student so I went to Germany
and she came here during my grade 11
year
which I'm going to talk about in my next
video on travel but when I came back my
friend group had changed and my best
friend I had to choosing to my two best
friends and the one that I chose had a
new group of girlfriends and I just
friends really and so that's who we hang
out with for the end of grade 11 in
grade 12 which was also characterized by
me falling in love with her brother who
I couldn't be with because he was away
at hockey but we wrote the letters back
and forth to each other and then right
before he got back he we weren't allowed
to start dating my best friend said it
wasn't it wasn't okay and I was just
like I'm done I'm done with this small
town bs and I moved to Vancouver where
my sister and dad were already already
living but one of the other
characteristics of my adolescents as
well as like holding on to this logic
was discovering that I was intelligent I
was told to go into remedial math
because I couldn't possibly handle
regular mainstream math so between grade
9 junior high and high school grade 10 I
chose to go into the remedial and when I
was there I got like 99% in all of all
of the tests which I think if I had been
put into regular math I wouldn't have
necessarily gotten 99% so I wouldn't
have felt intelligent I would have just
been probably a C student but because I
was an A student it somehow made me
realize I could be and was an A student
in everything I got a is throughout high
school having gotten definitely not is
in junior high and not paying attention
and it was kind of because this person
underestimated me and told me to go into
this did I then ended up realizing I was
intelligent and like I said I got
straight A's in school which is why I
was able to go on to University and also
why like the fact that my biology
teacher was one of my favorite teachers
she was just amazing taking physics
writing horrible stories in the back
with my friends and then AC net like the
night
before I would go in and get the
understand what was gonna be on the test
ace the test and then like forget it
after and I didn't take chemistry which
is the third science that was offered
and I didn't take calculus because I
thought that it was a I thought it was
like calculating I thought it was like a
counting in my head it was a counting
and so I didn't take it but what I did
take I was good at and it made me feel
intelligent and because I felt
intelligent I was able to get straight
A's so I feel like my adolescence
started with the falling away of
Christianity and ended when I moved out
from right after high school when I
moved to Vancouver because of this
heartbreak and pursuing like my dream of
going to university but also very much
leaving this small-town mentality behind